Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XXIX is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XXX is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XXIX. AMERICAN ARBITRATION ASSOCIATION
  - Sub-Series 244-0. American Arbitration Association
    - General, 1960-1964 (Box 159, Folder 1)
- Series XXX. INCREASES AND DECREASES BY LODGES
  - Sub-Series 250-0. Increases and Decreases by Lodges
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1946 (Box 159, Folder 2)
      Fourth Quarter, 1946.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1946 (Box 159, Folder 3)
      Second Quarter, 1946.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1946 (Box 159, Folder 4)
      Third Quarter, 1946.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1946 (Box 159, Folder 5)
      First Quarter, 1946.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1945 (Box 159, Folder 6)
      Fourth Quarter, 1945.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1945 (Box 159, Folder 7)
      Third Quarter, 1945.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1945 (Box 160, Folder 1)
      Second Quarter, 1945.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1945 (Box 160, Folder 2)
      First Quarter, 1945.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1948 (Box 160, Folder 3)
      Fourth Quarter, 1948.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1948 (Box 160, Folder 4)
      Third Quarter, 1948.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1948 (Box 160, Folder 5)
      Second Quarter, 1948.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1948 (Box 160, Folder 6)
      First Quarter, 1948.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1947 (Box 160, Folder 7)
      Fourth Quarter, 1947.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1947 (Box 160, Folder 8)
      Third Quarter, 1947.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1947 (Box 161, Folder 1)
      Second Quarter, 1947.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1947 (Box 161, Folder 2)
      First Quarter, 1947.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1951 (Box 161, Folder 3)
      First Quarter, 1951.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1950 (Box 161, Folder 4)
      Fourth Quarter, 1950.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1950 (Box 161, Folder 5)
      Third Quarter, 1950.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1950 (Box 161, Folder 6)
      Second Quarter, 1950.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1950 (Box 161, Folder 7)
      First Quarter, 1950.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1949 (Box 162, Folder 1)
      Third Quarter, 1949.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1949 (Box 162, Folder 2)
      Second Quarter, 1949.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1949 (Box 162, Folder 3)
      First Quarter, 1949.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1957 (Box 162, Folder 4)
      Fourth Quarter, 1957.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1957 (Box 162, Folder 5)
      Third Quarter, 1957.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1957 (Box 162, Folder 6)
      Second Quarter, 1957.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1957 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1957 (Box 162, Folder 8)
      First Quarter, 1957.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1957 (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1956 (Box 162, Folder 10)
      Fourth Quarter, 1956.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1956 (Box 163, Folder 1)
      Third Quarter, 1956.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1956 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1956 (Box 163, Folder 3)
      Second Quarter, 1956.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1956 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1956 (Box 163, Folder 5)
      First Quarter, 1956.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1956 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1955 (Box 163, Folder 7)
      Fourth Quarter, 1955.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1955 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1955 (Box 163, Folder 9)
      Third Quarter, 1955.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1955 (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1955 (Box 163, Folder 11)
      Second Quarter, 1955.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1955 (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1955 (Box 163, Folder 13)
      First Quarter, 1955.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1955 (Box 163, Folder 14)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1954 (Box 164, Folder 1)
      Fourth Quarter, 1954.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1954 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1954 (Box 164, Folder 3)
      Third Quarter, 1954.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1954 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1960 (Box 164, Folder 5)
      Fourth Quarter, 1960.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1960 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1960 (Box 164, Folder 7)
      Third Quarter, 1960.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1960 (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1960 (Box 164, Folder 9)
      Second Quarter, 1960.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1960 (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1960 (Box 164, Folder 11)
      First Quarter, 1960.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1960 (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1959 (Box 164, Folder 13)
      Fourth Quarter, 1959.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1959 (Box 164, Folder 14)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1959 (Box 164, Folder 15)
      Third Quarter, 1959.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1959 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1959 (Box 165, Folder 2)
      Second Quarter, 1959.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1959 (Box 165, Folder 3)
      First Quarter, 1959.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1959 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1958 (Box 165, Folder 5)
      Fourth Quarter, 1958.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1958 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1958 (Box 165, Folder 7)
      Third Quarter, 1958.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1958 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1958 (Box 165, Folder 9)
      Second Quarter, 1958.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1958 (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1958 (Box 165, Folder 11)
      First Quarter, 1958.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1958 (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1961 (Box 165, Folder 13)
      Fourth Quarter, 1961.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1961 (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1961 (Box 165, Folder 15)
      Third Quarter, 1961.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1961 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1961 (Box 166, Folder 2)
      Second Quarter, 1961.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1961 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1961 (Box 166, Folder 4)
      First Quarter, 1961.
    - Increases and Decreases by Lodges, 1961 (Box 166, Folder 5)